Hey everyone! In today's video I'm going to show you... I don't actually know what
I'm going to show you because I only have a box and I have no idea what's
inside. So today I'm going to present you the Honor Clothing Latex Mystery Box.
Okay let's open it. First glance no idea. Oh seamless fingerless like latex gloves.
Still no idea, I have to unpack it. Keyhole latex body and latex skater skirt. Wow, so complete outfit.
Okay, so the Anna Latex Mystery Box is a relatively new product in the Anna Workshop.
As it says mystery, you don't know what you're getting. You have three values to choose from.
150 pound, 200 pounds and 250 pounds. And today I'm going to show you the 200 pound box.
the bodysuit I love all the studs here
oh it's a skater skirt so cute I love skater skirts obviously one box contains a whole outfit
that is matching so they put thought into packing these so these are the gloves
and I am still curious about what's that ah yeah latex shiner now we have lots of
black latex and I'm going to change into it I got into it and it looks like a
dress but as I said it's a bodysuit and this is the back side also again bodysuit
this is fun and we have the fingerless gloves I shined it with the shiner that was in
the package I'm really happy with the outfit turn around again and I think it's a cool bargain
because let me calculate it for a bit this was a 200 pound box to get items roughly worth 220 pounds
and you know with my discount code Celine you can also save 20 percent so I think that's a good idea
if you need for example a gift because for whom is this box first of all for everyone who likes
to be surprised of course get this as a gift for someone for christmas for example christmas is
around the corner so you can order it now get it in time and also it's for people who can't decide
what to wear for example me i hate to decide what i'm going to wear just get an outfit which i can
wear but I don't have to choose it myself again I really love the outfit I'm a sucker for this
kind of riveted outfits I have matching shoes I love metal parts for example I could wear these
heels with them but I also am wearing different heels with rivets so this totally fits my style
thanks to honor for sending this over and whoever packed it good job anyway I hope you enjoyed this
video check out the on the mystery boxes I'll link them in the description text of course
there are different varieties just have a look at their webshop don't forget to use my code
for 20% off and happy shopping I will see you in the next video leave a comment and a thumbs up
see you around bye